http://www.preluderestoration.org/terms-conditions/

Search for:
Close
Search for:
Terms & Conditions
Home /
Terms & Conditions
INTRODUCTION
1.1. PURPOSE OF POLICY. {preluderestoration.org} (“us”, “we,” “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors and other users of { preluderestoration.org} (the “Site”). We created this Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices. This Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.
1.2.
NOTICE CONCERNING CHILDREN
PLEASE
NOTE: We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content
specifically at children under 13 years of age pursuant to the Children’s
Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998.
2.
INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES
2.1. WHAT
BASIC INFORMATION DOES THE COMPANY COLLECT?
In
operating the Site, we collect personal information from you in a couple
different situations. The first is if you should contact us via the “contact”
page. In doing so, you will provide us with your name and email address. The
second is if you leave a comment to a blog post during which you may be asked
for a name and other information. You are not required to provide us with
information via these two methods to use and enjoy the Site.
2.2. WHAT
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION DOES COMPANY COLLECT?
(a)
AUTOMATIC COLLECTION. Our
servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the
number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about
you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous “traffic
data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for
marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.
(b)
COOKIES. From
time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser
applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer
about your visit to our Site. Cookies help us learn which areas of our Site are
useful and which areas need improvement through programs including, but not
limited to, Google Analytics. We may also use cookies from third party social
sites and programs including, but not limited to, Facebook, Google Plus and
Twitter. You can choose to disable cookies through your browser or independent
programs available online. However, if you choose to disable this function,
your experience at our Site may be diminished as some features may not work as
they were intended.
(c)
SPONSORS AND ADVERTISERS. We may decide to accept sponsorship and advertisements on the Site.
Should this occur, you should assume said sponsors and advertisers will be
given access to the impressions and click data on their marketing pieces. Your
personally identifiable information will never be revealed to them by us.
3. USE
AND SHARING OF INFORMATION
3.1. WHAT
DOES COMPANY DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?
(a)
PERSONAL INFORMATION. We do not disclose the personally identifiable information to any third
parties other than those that we use to facilitate the functioning of the site
such as a hosting company and email program for mailings.
(b)
ANONYMOUS INFORMATION. We use
anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic. In addition, we may use
anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer
our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and
transaction information may also be shared with business partners and
advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.
(c) USE
OF COOKIES. Promotions
or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have
access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our
site.
(d)
DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We may disclose any information we have for you if
required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is
necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process
served on us, (2) protect and defend our rights or property or the users of the
Site, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the
public or users of the Site.
(e) SALE
OF INFORMATION. In order
to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of the Site
or our company, including the information collected through this Site. If Company
or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, user
information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.
4.
SECURITY
The Site
has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of
the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our
ability to prevent any such loss to you or to any third party arising out of
any such loss, misuse, or alteration.
5.
WEBSITE AREAS BEYOND COMPANY’S CONTROL
5.1.
THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
From
time-to-time, the Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to
visit those websites, it is important to understand our privacy practices and
terms of use do not extend to those sites. It is your responsibility to review
the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree
with their practices.
6.
CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES
6.1.
CONTACTING US
If you
have any questions about this Policy or our practices related to this Site,
please feel contact us using the “Contact” link on the menu located at the top
of the site.
6.2.
UPDATES AND CHANGES
We
reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this
Policy to reflect changes in our Privacy Policy. We shall post any such changes
on the Site in a conspicuous area. You may then choose whether you wish to
accept said policy changes or discontinue using the Site. Any such change,
update, or modification will be effective 30 days after posting on the Site. It
is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that
you continue to agree with all of its terms.
(a) If
you have signed up for email communications from us, we will notify you of the
privacy policy changes by email as well.
